Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Proposals Accepted & Funded, 1985-1992
  - Femmes Developpement Entreprise en Afrique. (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - G.R.A.D.E. - F.R.B. (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Uniao Geral das Cooperativas Agro-Pecuarias de Maputo (Mozambique). (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Global Exchange. (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Operation Crossroads Africa (Box 216, Folder 10-14)
    - BG 614. (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - BG 614. (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - BG 614. (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Financial - BG 614. (Box 216, Folder 14)
  - Tanzania Media Women's Association. (Box 216, Folder 13)
  - Organization of Mazambican Women (OMM). (Box 216, Folder 15)
  - Organization of Rural Association (ORAP). (Box 216, Folder 16)
  - Overseas Development Network (ODN). (Box 216, Folder 17)
  - Oxfam / America. (Box 216, Folder 18)
  - Promo Femmes / Developpement Sports. (Box 216, Folder 19)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI). (Box 216, Folder 20)
  - Sudan Council of Voluntary Agencies (Sudan Council of Voluntary Agencies (SCOVA). (Box 216, Folder 21)
  - Sudan Council of Churches. (Box 216, Folder 22)
  - Tanzania Media Women's Association - Children's songs., (Cassette) (Box 216, Folder 23)
  - Tanzania Media Women's Association (TAMWA). (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Third World Information Network (TWIN). (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Trickle-Up Program. (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) (Box 217, Folder 4-5)
    - Project summary - 08709. (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - 08709. (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - A.I.C.F. / Ethiopia - Financial report and final assessment., (1991) (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Institute of International Education - Working Paper no.17: South African Trusts / Foundations., (1991) (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Unitarian Universalists Service Committee - Proposal for primary health care in Eritrea., (1986) (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Beira low - Cost vehicle demonstration project (Mozambique) - Final report., (1991) (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - Rochester - Bamako emergency assistance project for maternal and child health care - Final report., (1989) (Box 217, Folder 10)
  - Management development through training and technical assistance - Final report., (1989) (Box 217, Folder 11)
  - Status report - East and Southern Africa., 1990 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Field monitoring report - West Africa., 1990 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - U.S.A. for Africa - Africa Development Education - grants program. (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - U.S.A. for Africa - Africa field monitoring report. (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - African - American Institute. (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Association of Women's Clubs - Zimbabwe. (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Ajuda de Desenvolvimento de Povo Para Povo (ADPP) - Mozambique. (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - World Education. (Box 218, Folder 8)
  - Association des Bacheliers pour l'Emploi et le Developpement (ABACED) - reports. (Box 218, Folder 9)
  - Food for the Hungry International / Ethiopia - report., October-December 1991 (Box 218, Folder 11)
  - Comite Regional Baha'i de Service Humanitaire pour le Developpement (CRBSHD). (Box 218, Folder 12)
  - International Union for the Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN) Sahel program (Box 218, Folder 13-15)
    - 6 month report., (January-June 1991) (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Progress report., (January-September 1991) (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - Progress report., (June-December 1991); (December 1990-December 1991). (Box 218, Folder 15)
      Scope and Contents
      [Also], Assessment report (December 1990-December 1991).
  - European Network on Debt and Development (EURODAD) - world development report., (1992) (Box 218, Folder 16)
  - European Network on Debt and Development (EURODAD) - various articles. (Box 218, Folder 17)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Angola, 1985-1992
  - Ajuda de Desenvolvimento de Povo para Povo (ADPP) (Box 202, Folder 1-5)
    - Correspondence - 10404. (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 10404. (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Financial - 10404. (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Procurement - 10404. (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Progress report - 10404. (Box 202, Folder 5)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Bukina Faso, 1985-1992
  - A.V.L.P. - Project summary - 01902. (Box 202, Folder 29)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Burkina Faso, 1985-1992
  - Association des Volontaires pour le developpement (AVD). (Box 209, Folder 29)
  - A.V.L.P. (Box 209, Folder 31)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Burkina Faso, 1985-1992
  - Burkina Faso. (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - A.D.B.N.L.O. - Women's Integrated Development (Box 202, Folder 7-9)
    - Correspondence - 01701. (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - 01701. (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Project summary - 01701. (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Bureau de Liaison des Organisations non Governementales et Associations (BLONGA) - institutional support (Box 202, Folder 10-12)
    - Correspondence - 01703. (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 01703. (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 01703. (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - G.R.A.D.E.-F.R.B. - Nabigtenga internal development (Box 202, Folder 13-15)
    - Correspondence - 01707. (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - 01707. (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - 01707. (Box 202, Folder 15)
  - l'Institut Africain pour le Devloppement Economique et Social-Formation - Lena development & training (Box 202, Folder 16-18)
    - Financial information - 01708. (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - 01708. (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - Project summary - 01708. (Box 202, Folder 18)
  - Promo-Sporto development project (Box 202, Folder 19-21)
    - Financial information - SEP0201. (Box 202, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - SEP0201. (Box 202, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - SEP0201. (Box 202, Folder 21)
  - S.P.O.N.G. - Non-governmental organization training (Box 202, Folder 22-24)
    - Correspondence - 01709. (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - 01709. (Box 202, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 01709. (Box 202, Folder 24)
  - A.V.L.P. (Box 202, Folder 25-28)
    - Financial information - 01710. (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - Project summary - 01710. (Box 202, Folder 26)
    - Financial information - 01902. (Box 202, Folder 27)
    - Progress report - 01902. (Box 202, Folder 28)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Chad, 1985-1992
  - Darna (Box 202, Folder 30-32)
    - Project summary - 02704. (Box 202, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - 02704. (Box 202, Folder 31)
    - Financial information - 02704. (Box 202, Folder 32)
  - Darna II (Box 203, Folder 1-4)
    - Chad. (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - 02702. (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - 02702. (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Project summary - 02702. (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - A.R.P.E.S. - Rehab irrigated rice (Box 203, Folder 5-7)
    - Financial information - 02701. (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - 02701. (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - 02701. (Box 203, Folder 7)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Ethiopia, 1985-1992
  - E.R.C. - Pastoralist rehabilitation (Box 203, Folder 8-11)
    - Financial information - 03R01. (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Progress report - 03R01. (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - 03R01. (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - 03R01. (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - Africare - ground water development (Box 203, Folder 12-14)
    - Project summary - 03702. (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 03702. (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - 03702. (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - E.O.C. - Worldia rehabilitation project (Box 203, Folder 15-19)
    - Progress report - 03403. (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - 03403. (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - 03403. (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 03403. (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - Pamphlets & report - 03403., (1986) (Box 203, Folder 19)
  - F.F.H.I. - water & health development program (Box 203, Folder 20-23)
    - Financial information - 03406. (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - 03406. (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - 03406. (Box 203, Folder 22)
    - Progress report - 03406. (Box 203, Folder 23)
  - A.I.C.F. - small water supply (Box 204, Folder 1-4)
    - Project summary - 03701. (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 03701. (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 03701. (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Progress report - 03701. (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Concern - integrated rural development (Box 204, Folder 5-8)
    - Financial information - 03703. (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 03703. (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Progress report - 03703. (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Project summary - 03703. (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - E.G.T. - Expanded health & nutrition (Box 204, Folder 9-12)
    - Progress reports - 03705. (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - 03705. (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 03705. (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 03705. (Box 204, Folder 12)
  - E.N.A.T.B. - Debreberhane soap making (Box 204, Folder 13-16)
    - Progress reports - 03706. (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - 03706. (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - 03706. (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - 03706. (Box 204, Folder 16)
  - Handicap International (Box 204, Folder 17-21)
    - Correspondence - 03707. (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 03707. (Box 204, Folder 18)
    - Progress reports - 03707. (Box 204, Folder 19)
    - Project summary - 03707. (Box 204, Folder 20)
    - Supplemental materials - 07204. (Box 204, Folder 21)
  - L.V.I.A. - irrigating peasant nurseries (Box 204, Folder 22-24)
    - Correspondence - 03708. (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - 03708. (Box 204, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 03708. (Box 204, Folder 24)
  - Treepeople - African fruit tree partnership (Box 204, Folder 25-28)
    - Project summary - 03709. (Box 204, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - 03709. (Box 204, Folder 26)
    - Progress reports - 03709. (Box 204, Folder 27)
    - Financial information - 03709. (Box 204, Folder 28)
  - P.I.E. (Box 205, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence - 03711. (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - 03711. (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - 03711. (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - A.C.R.C. (Box 205, Folder 4-6)
    - Correspondence - HNA08. (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Financial information - HNA08. (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - HNA08. (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Forum of Int's Development Organization c/o World College West - HNA09. (Box 205, Folder 7)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mali, 1985-1992
  - Save the Children - 04009. (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - A.D.C. II - Artisans capitalization (Box 205, Folder 9-11)
    - Project summary - 04701. (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - 04701. (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 04701. (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - Association pour le Dveloppement des Activits de Production et de Formation (ADAF-GALLE) - women's rice production (Box 205, Folder 12-14)
    - Correspondence - 04702. (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Project summary - 04702. (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - 04702. (Box 205, Folder 14)
  - Comit de Coordination des Actions des Organisations non Governementales (CCA-ONG) - support to CCA information (Box 205, Folder 15-16, 19)
    - Project summary - 04703. (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - 04703. (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - Financial information - 04703. (Box 205, Folder 19)
  - Secrtariat de Concertation des Organisations non Governementales (SECO-ONG) - Project summary - 04706. (Box 205, Folder 17)
  - Mali. (Box 205, Folder 18)
  - O.M.A.E.S. - Sikasso women's grain (Box 205, Folder 20-22)
    - Correspondence - 04705. (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - 04705. (Box 205, Folder 21)
    - Financial information - 04705. (Box 205, Folder 22)
  - Association Tassaght - 04709. (Box 205, Folder 23-24)
  - C.E.F.D.A.P./Oxfam (Box 206, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence - 04710. (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 04710. (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 04710. (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - International Service (UNAIS) - Mopti resettlement (Box 206, Folder 4-6)
    - Correspondence - 04R01. (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Financial information - 04R01. (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - 04R01. (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Association Kilabo (Box 206, Folder 7-10)
    - Project summary - 04401B. (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - 04401B. (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Progress report - 04401B - empty. (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 04401B. (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Terre des Hommes (Box 206, Folder 11-13)
    - Project summary - 05403. (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - 05403. (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 05403. (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) (Box 206, Folder 14-16)
    - Correspondence - 05404. (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 05404. (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - 05404. (Box 206, Folder 16)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mauritania, 1985-1992
  - Program Review Board packet. (Box 209, Folder 24)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Miscellaneous, 1985-1992
  - S.A.G. organization - S.A.G. - general information., 1991 (Box 209, Folder 23)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mozambique, 1985-1992
  - Community Aid Abroad (Box 206, Folder 17-20)
    - Correspondence - 06402. (Box 206, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 06402. (Box 206, Folder 18)
    - Progress report - 06402. (Box 206, Folder 19)
    - Project summary - 06402. (Box 206, Folder 20)
  - C.C.M. - Peri-Urban M.C.H. (Box 206, Folder 21-24)
    - Progress report - 06701. (Box 206, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - 06701. (Box 206, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - 06701. (Box 206, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 06701. (Box 206, Folder 24)
  - Ajuda de Desenvolvimento de Povo para Povo (ADPP) - street boy schools (Box 206, Folder 25-28)
    - Financial information - 06703. (Box 206, Folder 25)
    - Progress reports - 06703. (Box 206, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - 06703. (Box 206, Folder 27)
    - Project summary - 06703. (Box 206, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Transportation and Development Policy (ITDP) - bikes for Africa (Box 206, Folder 29-32)
    - Financial information - 06705. (Box 206, Folder 29)
    - Project summary - 06705. (Box 206, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - 06705. (Box 206, Folder 31)
    - Progress reports - 06705. (Box 206, Folder 32)
  - O.M.M. - grinding mills (Box 206, Box 207)
    - Financial information - 06706. (Box 206, Folder 33)
    - Project summary - 06706. (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Progress reports - 06706. (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - 06706. (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - U.G.C. (Box 207, Folder 4-7)
    - Correspondence - 06707. (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 06707. (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - 06707. (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Progress reports - 06707. (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Kulima - Correspondence. (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - U.S. COMM/UNICEF (Box 207, Folder 9-12)
    - Project reports - 06710. (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Communications - 06710. (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 06710. (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 06710. (Box 207, Folder 12)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Senegal, 1985-1992
  - Senegal. (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - A.R.D.E.C. - Community animal raising (Box 207, Folder 14-16)
    - Correspondence - 08701. (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 08701. (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - 08701. (Box 207, Folder 16)
  - Association des Jeunes Pour l'education et le Developpement (AJED) - Cattle & soil (Box 207, Folder 17-19)
    - Project summary - 08702. (Box 207, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - 08702. (Box 207, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - 08702. (Box 207, Folder 19)
  - Association of Youth for the promotion of Non-Wage-Earning Employment (AJUPENS) - Communal fishing project (Box 207, Folder 20-22)
    - Project summary - 08703. (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - 08703. (Box 207, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - 08703. (Box 207, Folder 22)
  - Le Fonds africain devloppement (FAFD) - literacy & numeracy - Correspondence - 08706. (Box 207, Folder 23-25)
    - Correspondence - 08706. (Box 207, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 08706. (Box 207, Folder 24)
    - Project summary - 08706. (Box 207, Folder 25)
  - F.D.E.A. - women's enterprises (Box 208, Folder 1-3)
    - Financial information - 08707. (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 08707. (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - 08707. (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - I.A.R.A. - Peykouk cattle (Box 208, Folder 4-6)
    - Correspondence - 08708. (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Financial information - 08708. (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - 08708. (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) - literacy & training - Casamang reports - 08709. (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Association de Bacheliers por l'Emploi et le Developpement (ABACED) - Project summary & correspondence - 08712. (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - A.J.A.C./Sans Frontiers (Box 208, Folder 9-11)
    - Correspondence - 08710. (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 08710. (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 08710. (Box 208, Folder 11)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Sudan, 1985-1992
  - A.U.F.W. - Women's Health Initiative Nile water project (Box 208, Folder 12-15)
    - Correspondence - 09701. (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 09701. (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 09701. (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Progress reports - 09701. (Box 208, Folder 15)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) / U.S. - women's co-operative (Box 208, Folder 16-19)
    - Correspondence - 09703. (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Progress reports - 09703. (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - Project summary - 09703. (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - 09703. (Box 208, Folder 19)
  - Rseau africain pour le dveloppement intgr Mali (RADI) (Box 208, Folder 20-24)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 208, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - 08409. (Box 208, Folder 21)
    - Progress report - 08409. (Box 208, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - 08409. (Box 208, Folder 23)
    - Financial report - 08409. (Box 208, Folder 24)
  - E.R.S.R.C.S. (Box 208, Folder 25-28)
    - Progress reports - 09R02. (Box 208, Folder 25)
    - Financial information - 09R02. (Box 208, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - 09R02. (Box 208, Folder 27)
    - Project summary - 09R02. (Box 208, Folder 28)
  - I.A.G. (Box 209, Folder 1-3)
    - Project summary - HNA06. (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - HNA06. (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - HNA06. (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - I.A.R.A. (Box 209, Folder 4-7)
    - Financial information - 09R03. (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Progress reports - 09R03. (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 09R03. (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Project summary - 09R03. (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Oxfam/U.S. - Fisheries (Box 209, Folder 8-11)
    - Correspondence - 09R04. (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - 09R04. (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 09R04. (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Progress reports - 09R04. (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) / U.S. (Box 209, Folder 12-15)
    - Correspondence - 09R05. (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 09R05. (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 09R05. (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - Progress reports - 09R05. (Box 209, Folder 15)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Tanzania, 1985-1992
  - Adventures in Health, Education and Agricultural Development (AHEAD), Incorporated. (Box 209, Folder 28)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Uganda, 1985-1992
  - Uganda National Council of Women (Box 209, Folder 16-19)
    - Correspondence - 20901. (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - 20901. (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 20901. (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - Progress report - 20901. (Box 209, Folder 19)
  - Marine Biological Station (Box 209, Folder 20-22)
    - Project summary - UD06101. (Box 209, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - UD06101. (Box 209, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - UD06101. (Box 209, Folder 22)
- RD II Rejected Proposals
  - Africa (Box 134, Box 135)
    - L.V.P.S. Manufacturer - 331. (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - M.C.H. training - San Diego State University - 232. (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Assorted target countries - Books for the World, Incorporated - 536. (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Healthcare - "CMI" - 525. (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Assorted countries - United Nations University / Institut National de la Recherche Agronomique (INRA) - 526. (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Vitamin A supplementation - 385. (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - International Emergency Relief Project - 563. (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Target countries - Survey of agricultural projects - 565. (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Africa / Sahel - Support fund to development Association - 402. (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Assorted countries - "Trickle Up" program - 524. (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Contingencies - African Non-governmental organizations's symposium - 421. (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Rural health worker training - 634. (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Center (OIC) International, Incorporated - Development & Institute of Human Resource Training - 635. (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Refugee policy group - Improving early warning refugee influxes - 636. (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Film project - development education - "The Quiet Revolution" - 564. (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Equator foundation - 715. (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - [Miscellaneous Africa] (Box 134, Box 135)
    - Africa / Sahel - Concept paper / role of media - 381. (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Africa / Sahel - Guarantee fund - Recherches et Applications de Financements alternatifs au Dveloppement (RAFAD) - 383. (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Africa / USA - "Early warning system disease" - Refugee policy group - 509. (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Africa / The Horn - Photo exhibit - 467 [empty]. (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) - West Africa promotion - South - South business promotion centers - 710. (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - America / South Africa - Angola speakers tour - 368. (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Angola (Box 135, Box 136)
    - Emergency medical treatment / prosthetics - 268. (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Citizens energy prosthesis workshop - 640. (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Increase of production of artificial limbs - 558. (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - School feeding program - 234. (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Save the Children Fund (SCF) program - 394. (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Fish Kuanza Sul - 631. (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Artificial limbs - 558. (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Primary health care program - 569. (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Ministry of Agriculture - 632. (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Cit. Energy - Fish drying - 639. (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Norwegian People's Aid - Integrated rural development - 711. (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Unlabelled folder - Mechanical cow - Vanguarda Mecanica - Brazil. (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Botswana (Box 136, Folder 3, 5-6)
    - Leadership training - 448. (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - "Broiler growing process" - 449. (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - YMCA multi purpose center - 450. (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Burkina Faso (Box 136, Box 137, Box 138)
    - Miscellaneous - Letters of support. (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Primary Health Care (PHC) in Sanguie province. (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Programme de development de la Communaute villageoise de Sagassiamasso. (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Vtrinaires sans frontires (VSF) - 1. Vet services - 2. Pig breeding. (Box 136, Folder 10)